{
    "subject": "resource/List_of_Boston_Public_episodes",
    "predicate": "property/directedby",
    "object": "resource/Alex_Graves",
    "human_readable": "Alex Graves directed Boston Public episodes.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8763077259063721,
            "question": "Who directed episodes of Boston Public?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8523163199424744,
            "question": "What was Alex Graves' role in the production of Boston Public?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6491916179656982,
            "question": "What TV show did Alex Graves direct episodes for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5738450288772583,
            "question": "Alex Graves is known for directing which type of program?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5074544548988342,
            "question": "Can you name another TV show directed by Alex Graves?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4956100881099701,
            "question": "Besides directing, what other roles might Alex Graves have had in the television industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48907384276390076,
            "question": "Did Alex Graves direct any episodes of a popular TV series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4831920266151428,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who worked on Boston Public?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43015527725219727,
            "question": "Name a TV show that Alex Graves worked on."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20530861616134644,
            "question": "What genre of television programming is Boston Public?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alex Graves directed Boston Public episodes.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2190_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a TV show that Alex Graves worked on.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2190_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the director who worked on Boston Public?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2190_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Alex Graves direct any episodes of a popular TV series?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2190_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2190_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2190_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2190_151.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2190_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2190_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2190_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2190_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2190_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2190_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2190_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to document 83.txt, Alex Graves' career credits include \"Boston Public\", among other shows."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Alex Graves has directed episodes of various TV shows, including \"Boston Public,\" which supports the statement that Alex Graves directed episodes of \"Boston Public.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}